kolcraft.com 2016-10-11

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy  **

By using or accessing this website you signify your acknowledgment and assent to the Privacy Policy (hereinafter “Policy”) set forth below. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use this website. Kolcraft can revise this Policy at any time by updating this posting, and your use after such change signifies your acceptance of the changed terms. Please check this Policy periodically for changes. This Policy is intended to help you understand how Kolcraft Enterprises, Inc. collects, uses and safeguards the information you provide on our Website.

**Personal Data**

If you browse the Website, you may generally do so anonymously without providing any personal information. However, there are cases in which we may ask you for personal data. For example, we will occasionally conduct on-line surveys to better understand the needs and profile of our visitors. In addition, we may request personal information when you register to receive additional information regarding our products and services, sign up for a newsletter, or send us a question. Even if you choose not to give information we request, you can still visit most of the Kolcraft website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services.

In case you change your mind or wish to update or delete personal information (such as your zip code), we will endeavor to correct, update or remove the personal data you give us. You can do this by contacting the Webmaster below.

**Orders**

When you place an order for a product, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This personal information is required so that we can process and fulfill your order, send an order or shipping confirmation, as well as notify you of your order status.

**E-Mail Subscription**

If you provide us with personal information, and choose to join our email list, we will e-mail you regarding product updates, special offers, new products, and other information such as product recalls. If you do not wish to receive e-mail updates, please contact our Webmaster at the address below. Moreover, Kolcraft will not share your e-mail address with third parties for promotional purposes, except when you consent to such sharing by explicitly opting in to our partner e-mail list.

**Email Preferences/Opt-out**

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or other promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them at any time. Follow the ‘Unsubscribe’ link included in the email or contact us at [webmaster@kolcraft.com](mailto:webmaster@kolcraft.com).

**Use of Personal Data**

Personal information provided by users who are 18 or more years of age may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Kolcraft and affiliates. Kolcraft does not share your personal information entered on this site with third-parties, except as outlined in this section.

The information that you give us (with the exception of your email address) and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. Kolcraft will not use your e-mail address for marketing purposes unless you expressly opt-in to our e-mail list and we will not share your e-mail address with third parties for promotional purposes. We may also share your information as required by law. While we use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, Kolcraft will have no liability for disclosure of any information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third- parties.

Kolcraft also reserves the right to change or update this Policy, at any time, with reasonable notice to users of this Website. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Website.

**Cookies and IP Tracking**

This Website may use cookies for site administration purposes. No personal information is collected by these cookies. If for any reason you wish to not take advantage of cookies, you may have your browser not accept them, although this may disable or render unusable some of the features of the Kolcraft website.

This website also may detect and use your IP address or domain name for internal traffic monitoring and capacity purposes or to otherwise administer our website. No personal information is obtained; rather, just the patterns of usage of our various users may be tracked to provide you with improved service and content based on aggregate or statistical reviews of user site traffic patterns.

**Special Cases**

Kolcraft reserves the right to disclose user information in special cases, when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Kolcraft website users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information without notice to you in response to a subpoena or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to respond to an emergency situation.

**Policies for Children**

Kolcraft encourages parents and guardians to monitor and participate in their children’s online activities. Unless you are viewing a website directed specifically to children, no information should be submitted to this site by users under 13 years of age, and users less than 13 years old are not allowed to register for newsletters, clubs or activities. In addition, users less than 18 years of age are not allowed to make purchases or participate in contests, except for those specifically directed to children. Where appropriate, Kolcraft may ask you to indicate your age to verify compliance with these policies.

Kolcraft does not knowingly collect information from our guests under 13 years of age or provide any personally identifying information from such guests to any third party for any reason whatsoever. We do not allow guests known to be under 13 years of age to receive direct marketing communications from Kolcraft or from third parties.

**Contact Information:**

Kolcraft Enterprises, Inc.   
Attention: Webmaster  
1100 W. Monroe St.

Chicago, Illinois 60607

Questions about our products should not be directed to this address and will not be replied to. Questions about our products should be addressed to [customerservice@kolcraft.com](mailto:customerservice@kolcraft.com).

©2016 Kolcraft Enterprises, Inc., All Rights Reserved.
